[
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 0",
        "front": "井",
        "back": "우물 정"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 1",
        "front": "尋",
        "back": "찾을 심"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 2",
        "front": "團",
        "back": "둥글 단"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 3",
        "front": "角",
        "back": "뿔 각"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 4",
        "front": "陽",
        "back": "볕 양"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 5",
        "front": "引",
        "back": "끌 인"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 6",
        "front": "至",
        "back": "이를 지"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 7",
        "front": "鶴",
        "back": "학 학"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 8",
        "front": "紅",
        "back": "붉을 홍"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 9",
        "front": "悔",
        "back": "뉘우칠 회"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 10",
        "front": "逆",
        "back": "거스를 역"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 11",
        "front": "佳",
        "back": "아름다울 가"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 12",
        "front": "登",
        "back": "오를 등"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 13",
        "front": "危",
        "back": "위태할 위"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 14",
        "front": "充",
        "back": "채울 충"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 15",
        "front": "浴",
        "back": "목욕할 욕"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 16",
        "front": "章",
        "back": "글 장"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 17",
        "front": "初",
        "back": "처음 초"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 18",
        "front": "貴",
        "back": "귀할 귀"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 19",
        "front": "囚",
        "back": "가둘 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 20",
        "front": "相",
        "back": "서로 상"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 21",
        "front": "詳",
        "back": "자세할 상"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 22",
        "front": "件",
        "back": "물건 건"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 23",
        "front": "巾",
        "back": "수건 건"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 24",
        "front": "蘭",
        "back": "난초 난(란)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 25",
        "front": "亂",
        "back": "어지러울 난(란)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 26",
        "front": "掃",
        "back": "쓸 소"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 27",
        "front": "所",
        "back": "바 소"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 28",
        "front": "後",
        "back": "뒤 후"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 29",
        "front": "厚",
        "back": "두터울 후"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 30",
        "front": "舌",
        "back": "혀 설"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 31",
        "front": "雪",
        "back": "눈 설"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 32",
        "front": "器",
        "back": "그릇 기"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 33",
        "front": "奇",
        "back": "기특할 기"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 34",
        "front": "武",
        "back": "호반 무"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 35",
        "front": "舞",
        "back": "춤출 무"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 36",
        "front": "邑",
        "back": "고을 읍"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 37",
        "front": "泣",
        "back": "울 읍"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 38",
        "front": "玉",
        "back": "구슬 옥"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 39",
        "front": "蜜",
        "back": "꿀 밀"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 40",
        "front": "寫",
        "back": "베낄 사"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 41",
        "front": "星",
        "back": "별 성"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 42",
        "front": "走",
        "back": "달릴 주"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 43",
        "front": "太",
        "back": "클 태"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 44",
        "front": "快",
        "back": "쾌할 쾌"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 45",
        "front": "笠",
        "back": "삿갓 립(입)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 46",
        "front": "葉",
        "back": "잎 엽"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 47",
        "front": "重",
        "back": "무거울 중"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 48",
        "front": "酒",
        "back": "술 주"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 49",
        "front": "夏",
        "back": "여름 하"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 50",
        "front": "得",
        "back": "얻을 득"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 51",
        "front": "歸",
        "back": "돌아갈 귀"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 52",
        "front": "比",
        "back": "견줄 비"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 53",
        "front": "旦",
        "back": "아침 단"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 54",
        "front": "責",
        "back": "꾸짖을 책"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 55",
        "front": "電",
        "back": "번개 전"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 56",
        "front": "必",
        "back": "반드시 필"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 57",
        "front": "氣壓",
        "back": "기압"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 58",
        "front": "要因",
        "back": "요인"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 59",
        "front": "遂行",
        "back": "수행"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 60",
        "front": "當然",
        "back": "당연"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 61",
        "front": "葡萄糖",
        "back": "포도당"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 62",
        "front": "供給",
        "back": "공급"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 63",
        "front": "生産",
        "back": "생산"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 64",
        "front": "原理",
        "back": "원리"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 65",
        "front": "絕對的",
        "back": "절대적"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 66",
        "front": "垂直的",
        "back": "수직적"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 67",
        "front": "婚姻",
        "back": "혼인"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 68",
        "front": "擴大",
        "back": "확대"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 69",
        "front": "別途",
        "back": "별도"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 70",
        "front": "途中",
        "back": "도중"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 71",
        "front": "疑問",
        "back": "의문"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 72",
        "front": "哀惜",
        "back": "애석"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 73",
        "front": "等",
        "back": "~등(무리 등)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 74",
        "front": "登校",
        "back": "등교"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 75",
        "front": "驅使",
        "back": "구사"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 76",
        "front": "結局",
        "back": "결국"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 77",
        "front": "價値",
        "back": "가치"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 78",
        "front": "拒否",
        "back": "거부"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 79",
        "front": "內在",
        "back": "내재"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 80",
        "front": "變化",
        "back": "변화"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 81",
        "front": "隨伴",
        "back": "수반"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 82",
        "front": "發達",
        "back": "발달"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 83",
        "front": "流通",
        "back": "유통"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 84",
        "front": "漸次",
        "back": "점차"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 85",
        "front": "失敗",
        "back": "실패"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 86",
        "front": "投資",
        "back": "투자"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 87",
        "front": "時節",
        "back": "시절"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 88",
        "front": "一石二鳥",
        "back": "일석이조"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 89",
        "front": "大統領",
        "back": "대통령"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 90",
        "front": "指導者",
        "back": "지도자"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 91",
        "front": "世上",
        "back": "세상"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 92",
        "front": "衝擊",
        "back": "충격"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 93",
        "front": "慰勞",
        "back": "위로"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 94",
        "front": "獻金",
        "back": "헌금"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 95",
        "front": "沒頭",
        "back": "몰두"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 96",
        "front": "全國",
        "back": "전국"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 97",
        "front": "報償",
        "back": "보상"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 98",
        "front": "呼訴",
        "back": "호소"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 99",
        "front": "强調",
        "back": "강조"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 100",
        "front": "均",
        "back": "고를 균"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 101",
        "front": "專攻",
        "back": "전공"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 102",
        "front": "履修",
        "back": "이수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 103",
        "front": "判斷力",
        "back": "판단력"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 104",
        "front": "限定",
        "back": "한정"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 105",
        "front": "卷",
        "back": "책 권"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 106",
        "front": "冊",
        "back": "책 책"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 107",
        "front": "王歷",
        "back": "왕력"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 108",
        "front": "命令",
        "back": "명령"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 109",
        "front": "民俗",
        "back": "민속"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 110",
        "front": "豊富",
        "back": "풍부"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 111",
        "front": "內容",
        "back": "내용"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 112",
        "front": "成立",
        "back": "성립"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 113",
        "front": "政治",
        "back": "정치"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 114",
        "front": "交易",
        "back": "교역"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 115",
        "front": "新鮮",
        "back": "신선"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 116",
        "front": "外面",
        "back": "외면"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 117",
        "front": "塚",
        "back": "무덤 총"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 118",
        "front": "墓",
        "back": "무덤 묘"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 119",
        "front": "墳",
        "back": "무덤 분"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv40 - 120",
        "front": "寡",
        "back": "적을 과"
    }
]